<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on APS - WORKSHOP</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on APS - WORKSHOP</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>admin</title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Ford</title>
      <link>/authors/robert-ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/robert-ford/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/felipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/felipe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a Ph.D. candidate at the Department of Plant Pathology of the Ohio State University (OSU). My doctorate research is focused on the epidemiology study of Gibberella ear rot (&lt;em&gt;Fusarium gramearum&lt;/em&gt;), a disease that cause yield and grain quality reduction, and mycotoxin contamination on maize (&lt;em&gt;Zea mays&lt;/em&gt;). Under the mentorship of professor Paul, and co-advisor by professor Madden, we are studying the weather factors associated with this disease and mycotoxin contamination, hybrid stability, developing a risk assessment, chemical control, and more. On parallel of my Ph.D. research, I work with quantitative reviews, using meta-analytic models to summarise multiples studies. Other activities include presenting workshops on statistic methods and software use (as R or SAS), and leadership positions at American Phytopathology Society (APS) and Plant Pathology Graduat Student Association (PPGSA) of OSU.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before joining the Plant Pathology program of OSU, I earn my agronomy master degree under mentorship of professor Del Ponte, at the Federal University of Rio Grande do Sul, studying Soybean Rust. During my undergrad course, I also work on several plant pathology projects on field crops, under supervision of professor Balardin.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/paul/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/authors/paul/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
